With Hue Let's Call On Stage Once Again Man
Desai Chiray Mistry Om But My Self
and Saumya Joshi A big round of applause for
this stage which is from Ahmedabad, Gujarat
and Gujarati theatre. In general
Gujarati or Hindi stage arts and
creation, Saubha Joshi's name is very far
ahead. Her plays which have been multiple hits
like Welcome Zindagi 102 Not Out
Aaj Jaane Ki Jidd Na Karo and Pahalani Pol
Ke How many people have seen all these plays Make
Some
Noise and those who have not seen all these shows, don't watch
this show first, then
you will know what entertainment is and
that too especially in our language. Use Plus for
Saumya Joshi Everybody Come
On Saubhai, it is a pleasure to share the stage with you today. It is a
very good
space to be in. To be in the same space where you are
sitting on stage and I must tell you the
feeling is not
Mutual is the reason why I am
coming on stage after almost ten years because I want to
see you all and you are all very naked
people and the
way you introduced me,
this space and this and that and everything like that is
my image so
everything that has been created is that you will destroy it in 15-20 minutes.
I came here with the feeling that I am
highly low on
confidence. Let me tell you one reason for that. First,
my father asked me what to
do. So I said, "My friend, I do
n't know what to do.
So I can't explain this to you. But he
said that I want to do a love song. So
he first said that I will do B-
Edge
[music] on stage.
And out of curiosity, he asked me what to do. So
I said, "These people
know you all. So I said, 'It will be
like an interview.'"
People will humor everything,
so you should be careful
not to make jokes that require effort, or if I
told them this, then here they burst into
laughter, so
I came from home with such confidence,
now do whatever you want to do, don't
say anything, we don't do anything like that, the
public is sitting here, saying such
words, just now, that one who came wearing that one on his head,
sent it back,
sent it back, didn't do anything,
everything is fine, man, you know, we are very close to each other, and our
image has become very bad,
people say that you swear a lot,
your humor has a lot of double meaning, let me
say this and it won't sound like a bell, it's
wrong, man, don't use this language, okay, sorry for this, okay, deep, man, don't do this,
now we have a group of three, from
today you decide whether you want me in the
group or not.  There is a group of three, the
name of the group has been given since today,
but I think Swami Bhai has talked to you
that whether the language is important or not, whether it works
without the language or not,
this is not the language, these are just people, if
we people are performance performers, we
cannot work without the audience and this
audience says that it cannot work without the language,
so we have to say that it does not work, then
this is my answer, this is the
answer for this audience, I have it, and
Soumya Bhai means for me, I was very
surprised. When
I met Soumya Bhai for the first time and
we had many long discussions on the phone,
he is a big fan of Katko, a very
big fan of Katko, a very big fan and he
shows everyone Katko till this day,
so I was very surprised that
my idol, my hero loves my work, which is
my most famous work till now, it is one of the
most creative.  Things
I Have Seen It's Me and I can honestly
say that it has been constructed very beautifully,
all the
rules of the script and all the rules that are taught in the workshops have been
followed. It's not ours, it's not
yours, but it came from within you and did
n't go away.
I felt that it was something. It's
your permanent value of life. It
came from within, so it all fit perfectly into the rules. That's why
I
show it in my writing workshops too.
How comedy can be constructed
and how in a short time, I do
n't understand whether you say it's good or bad. I say it's
very good. I say it's extremely good. If you were to say it, then
add four more beats [of music]. We were just
talking backstage a while ago, which was a very raw format. The
pieces of this show, from that, we jump towards yours.
Kind of art
form you are the purest in your own way I
think and I look up to you and
at the same time we also talked about Broadway
back then or Pahalani Pol but when I
saw it I wondered how many
people have seen Pahalani Pol so much here so few
shouted man I mean I am so glad 300
shows have been done and such an illiterate audience is sitting here that it doesn't have it
but now what do you think Swami sir that
now our art form or ours you
write and work for Hindi too but
where should the Gujarati stage go now which
direction should it go I think Gujarati stage
means Gujarati audience is amazing it has been
watching plays like addicts for 150 years like the prisoners of war
so nothing has happened to that industry it has not moved
even if the worst of the worst work continues for decades poor people are struggling and  So it's only up to us
artists to serve good things
and whoever serves it like that, it's a
great response, like Welcome Zindagi, 1000
shows are going to be done, 300 shows of Pada Report are about to be
completed, 102 not out, about 400-500
shows have been done, so overall there is a huge
audience for very good content in
Gujarati and another nice and interesting thing is
that a nice and interesting transition is happening from
Gujarati stage to Gujarati films
and I feel that due to that the
quality of films will also get better and I think both the
industries will do well together. The beautiful answer was
no, yes,
clap for the answer, brother, the applause was like that,
so they will say again that
if you come to Gujarati industry, it will become a nuisance again, that's not something
I thought like that, I used to
ask us.  Where is the Gujarati audience
going? If we say Canada, we have
more. Yes, Broadway. I
think Broadway is where anyone has seen a Broadway play in life. We are only four or five people.
Someone will shout and attack us from 300 feet.
Now, if I went to New York,
there was a play called "We Merry We Go Together" in which
Daniel Radcliffe and
Jonathan Groff are playing. Daniel Radcliffe is the
Harry Potter guy. His ticket was for
Rs. 25,000. No, really. And
I bought four tickets in which I, Vidya
Zakir and his brother were. That Ben's
first thought was that he would get a two-year LPG.
But for those who don't know the context,
Broadway is a musical theater in which
people book an auditorium for almost years
and there the same play is
played there every day or almost on some days with so much
production.  Value or like this, after
watching more than four videos with your eyes, your brain goes crazy and you get that
experience, that same
reaction comes but in the positive, that hey this is happening,
first it was like that, hey then hey, our first
time was on
Broadway in 2018, we went to see Book of Mormon
and when we reached there,
we realized that we were the most
underdressed because those people were wearing suits and
then good pants and all the
gowns and both of us were wearing Dandiya Bazaar's Chaddas, that's why we were
dressed very underdressed,
sir, which Broadway have you seen? I have just
seen Phantom, Phantom of the Opera
and Lion King, oh, the all-time
classic, yes, I have seen both of these, and everyone else has
not seen them because the
ticket
was 25000 rupees. This is your 800, 800, they are doing all the business. I have
not seen my Padani Pol just now, so how many people want to see Padani Pol?
Mix-up  Noise Come On Yes,
I can now see Broadway.
Om's B Last Year was my first Broadway
experience. Yes, it was very, very fun. Was it
very fun? Ours was the best
experience. You guys had a good time.
Now, I would have liked to see B Ramuk
first. I liked doing Sole. Then
Sole. If I didn't like it, brother Ramu. Alya.
Contact is like that. That's why these people
keep tickets for 25,000 so that no
one can say after coming out that it's not fun. It's fun.
After spending 25,000, you are left with no option. No
one will say that after coming out, it's not fun like manipulation. You never saw that Journey. You went from
theater to film. I think
you liked it. As a one,
I saw Journey. In 102 Not Out, I
saw that Journey. Yes, yes, yes,
and yes.  The two most
legendary people of Indian cinema,
Amitabh Bachchan and Rishi Kapoor,
were both in the picture and what a brilliant play. Personally, I will be very honest. I love
the play more than the
film. I love that film.
But I didn't get any pleasure from it.
Because I was living here, everyone said that
people liked the play more.
So, it actually made 60 crores. In the
Indian market, when I
go outside Ahmedabad, I am not for that
film or 102 not out film or writer. And when I am
here or the play is not fun,
I always give one answer.
Man, you get married and go to Goa for honeymoon
and then go back there after a year. There is
always a difference in the fun of the two. You have
seen the play first, so that is the difference. The
main thing is that there is a great analogy. You go for a walk after a year
and then  Why didn't you enjoy it? But even
Soumya Joshi is so amazing
at his art and sorry sir, there have been too
many compliments but keep it up.
Reels are his guilty pleasure.
Friends, he is a doom scroller like us who
watches reels for two hours before going to sleep at night
and he has a guilty pleasure in it.
He enjoys it a lot. No, I don't have a
guilty pleasure in it because I
grew up on the Ketli of Ahmedabad. As an artist, I
feel that those Ketli have
diminished in some way and memes have
replaced the same atmosphere. Wow, if
you watch memes for half an hour, then
I get the whole experience of the Ketli on which we used to do the tricks and the madness that was going on. That's why I go every night, I go back to
that
nostalgia. Wow, what's the matter, you like the
art in you.  That's why you
made something like memes so beautiful,
yes because before this we were
talking about that vada pav thing,
so there is a beautiful thing like memes,
man people put dalvada in the oximeter during Covid,
now what
can be more beautiful than this, man patients were laughing on ventilators, it was
very technical, only some of you know,
but what is your favorite reel?
I like it and that slapstick one very much,
especially our Kushal Mistry,
Ahmedabadi Man, I like his reel very much, like
Pushpa's just arrived, and there is that
dance step of Pushpa, and this guy, sir,
this guy, like Pushpa, Pushpa, then he
turns the tea and puts it back in the glass like this,
it is still on the kettle, if it doesn't come on memes, then
he turns it like this, and if Kushal
turns like this, it sticks all over the wall, it's not fun, it's
not fun, when his mother wakes up like this,
or Topa  There I did it, it's
fun to stand up, that's why slapstick humor, I think
slapstick humor is very missing these days, from mainstream
comedy, yes, and
creativity is amazing, that's why
I keep flying in Modi Saheb's voice
[applause]
Over perfect bro, the confidence with which he
said that our national bird and
Modiji and then the cut was
brilliant
[applause], the
cut was
visible, that ladies and gentlemen,
thank you so much, very
nice, I said in the air,
I'm going to go in the khata, I said, look at the sky and the
land